kenkai.com 2007-12-15

# Kenkai SEO, web desigb, website redesign, search engine optimsation

Kenkai.com and SEO Insite Limited are committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of visitors to our web sites as well as the privacy of our actual customers. Our purpose in collecting information from you is to help us provide you with better service, such as notifications about special offers and promotions. We will not willfully disclose any individually identifiable information about you to any third party without first receiving your permission, as explained in this privacy statement. Kenkai.com and SEO Insite Limited does not collect individually identifiable information from any end-user. Furthermore, we do not specifically target children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly collect, without parental consent, individually identifiable information from such. Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices available for review. 

## Visitors

For visitors, we've structured our web sites so that, in general, you can visit us on the web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. When you visit our web site, our web server collects basic user information about you that includes your ISP's domain, the time you accessed our web site, and the pages from within our web site that you visit. Our web server does not collect your e-mail address or aggregate information on what other pages on the Web you have accessed or visited. The basic user information collected is used to help us analyze web traffic and to improve the content of our web site. We may from time to time disclose to third parties aggregate information on our web site's traffic profile. 

## Clients/Customers

We request information from the user on our contact form. Here a user must provide contact information. This information is used for replying to requests, billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers and link partners). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement within the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

## Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Kenkai.com and SEO Insite Limited, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

## Surveys

From time-to-time our site may request information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

## Security

This web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, the information is protected both online and off-line.

All of our users' information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected.

## Disclaimer

Kenkai.com and SEO Insite Limited disclaims any intention to censor, edit, or engage in ongoing review or surveillance of communications stored on or transmitted through its facilities by customers or others. Kenkai.com and SEO Insite Limited will, however, review, delete, or block access to communications that may harm Kenkai.com and SEO Insite Limited, its customers or third parties. The grounds on which Kenkai.com and SEO Insite Limited may take such action include, but are not limited to, actual or potential violations of Kenkai.com and SEO Insite Limited Policies. Please note, however, that Kenkai.com and SEO Insite Limited reserves the right to send bulletins and other important information regarding our services at our discretion.

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
